A Guide to the Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084 FA934
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Extant Faculty L-O, Miklos Muller, 1964-2000 (Box 24)
- Extinct Faculty A-Be, 1967-1985 (Box 24)
- Alexson, Stefan (Box 24)
- Alferov, V. V. (Box 24)
- Allman, David (Box 24)
- Aronson, Nathan N., Jr. (Box 24)
- Baggiolini, Marco (Box 24)
- Beard, Margaret (Box 24)
- Extinct Faculty Be (Box 24)
- Berberian, Paul A. (Box 24)
- Beyer, Carl Fredrick, Jr. (Box 24)
- Extinct Faculty, Be-C, 1972-1985 (Box 25)
- Bilbruck, John (Box 25)
- Black, William (Box 25)
- Bowers, William E. (Box 25)
- Chudzik, Jerzy (Box 25)
- Coffey, John W. (Box 25)
- Cohen, Gerald (Box 25)
- Cuevas, Dean (Box 25)
- Czako-Graham, Maria (Box 25)
- Extinct Faculty, D-E, 1967-1989 (Box 25)
- Daley, James (Box 25)
- Declerck, Paul (Box 25)
- Despommier, Dickson (Box 25)
- Deter, Russell L. (Box 25)
- Donaldson, Robert P. (Box 25)
- Ennis, Robert S. (Box 25)
- Etzion, Zipora (Box 25)
- Extinct Faculty, F, 1964-1998 (Box 25)
- Falcone, Dominick J. (Box 25)
- Farquhar, Marilyn G. (Box 25)
- Finkenstaedt, John T. (Box 25)
- Flatmark, Torgeir (Box 25)
- Fong, Dunne (Box 25)
- Fowler, Stanley (Box 25)
- Fujiki, Yukio (Box 25)
- Extinct Faculty, H-I, 1967-1994 (Box 25)
- Harrison, Earl H. (Box 25)
- Hajjar, David P. (Box 25)
- Haley, Nancy Jean (Box 25)
- Hagashi, Tokuhiko (Box 25)
- Hogg, James F. and Sylvia A. Cline (Box 25)
- Hornig, Joanna (Box 25)
- Horvat, Agnes (Box 25)
- Imanaka, Tsuneo (Box 25)
- Extinct Faculty, J-La, 1963-1990 (Box 25)
- Johnson, Patricia (Box 25)
- Kaplan-Bresler, Ann E. (Box 25)
- Keithly, Jan S. (Box 25)
- Keilian, Margaret (Box 25)
- Klinkert, Wolfgang (Box 25)
- Kondrup, Jens (Box 25)
- Krisans, Skaidrite (Box 25)
- LaBadie, Jon H. (Box 25)
- DeSales Lawless, B. (Box 25)
- Lacy, Peter Stephen (Box 25)
- Lanners, Norbert (Box 25)
- LaRusso, Nicholas F. (Box 25)
- Lazarow, Paul, 1971-2001 (Box 26)
- Extinct Faculty, Leighton, 1964-1992 (Box 26)
- Extinct Faculty, N-Pi, 1969-1998 (Box 26)
- Nehemiah, Jerome L. (Box 26)
- N'Seka (Box 26)
- Ohkuma, Shoji (Box 26)
- Omer, E. E. (Box 26)
- Perkins, Margaret (Box 26)
- Pirson, Philippe (Box 26)
- Peters, Timothy J. (Box 26)
- Panagides, John (Box 26)
- Piron, Agnes-Marie (Box 26)
- Extinct Faculty, Poole, 1965-1983 (Box 26)
- Poole, Elizabeth Davidson (Box 26)
- Reinhardsbrunn (Castle), 1981 (Box 26)
- Poole, Brian (Box 26)
- Extinct Faculty, Q-S, 1970-1991 (Box 26)
- Rachubinski, Richard (Box 26)
- Redwood, Charles S. (Box 26)
- Robbi, Mariette (Box 26)
- Sam-Yellowe, Tobili (Box 26)
- Santos, Manuel (Box 26)
- Schneider, Donald L. (Box 26)
- Shorr, Beth (Box 26)
- Shio, Helen (Box 26)
- Simon, Eliot (Box 26)
- Small, Gillian (Box 26)
- Soave, Rosemary (Box 26)
- Sullivan, Cathleen (Box 26)
- Sun, Alexander (Box 26)
- Szabo, Leslie J. (Box 26)
- Extinct Faculty, T, 1965-1991 (Box 26)
- Takano, Tatsuya (Box 26)
- Tappel, Aloys L. (Box 26)
- Thieringer, Rolf (Box 26)
- Tulkens, Genevieve and Paul (Box 26)
- Extinct Faculty, V-Z, 1971-1987 (Box 27)
- Volkl, Alfred (Box 27)
- Warburton, Michael (Box 26)
- Weber, Christopher R. (Box 26)
- Wibo, Maurice (Box 27)
- Wolinskty, Harvey (Box 27)
- Wong, Laurence (Box 27)
- Wong, Laurence (Box 27)
- Yago, Nagasumi (Box 27)
- Yago, Nagasumi (Box 27)
- Yarlett, Nigel (Box 27)
- Yau, Annie, Heart Association Fellowship (Box 27)
- Yau, Annie, Young Books (Box 27)
- Zbuzek, Vratislav (Box 27)
- Extinct Non-Faculty, A-L, 1964-1983 (Box 27)
- Arcario, Annette (Box 27)
- Buck, Sandra J. (Box 27)
- Burdick, Anne (Box 27)
- Chew, Nancy J. (Box 27)
- Cohen, Leonard (Box 27)
- Conley, Barbara (Box 27)
- Cucillo, Wendy (Box 27)
- Davidson, Fred (Box 27)
- de Backer, Diane (Box 27)
- Debbaudt, Madeleine (Box 27)
- de Helt, Claudine (Box 27)
- de Simone, Paula (Box 27)
- Dennis, Minnie, 1982 (Box 27)
- Eton, Willenor (Box 27)
- Feng, Natalie (Box 27)
- Fowler, Maryann (Box 27)
- Greene, Ronni (Box 27)
- Jacques, Patrick (Andre) (Box 27)
- Katz, Bruria (Box 27)
- Klein, Shelly (Box 27)
- Koss, Bogumila (Box 27)
- Lee, Pauline (Box 27)
- Kurtz, Gail (Box 27)
- Lin, Yi-Sheng John (Box 27)
- Extinct Non-Faculty, N-Z, 1965-1986 (Box 27)
- Marshall, Jonathan (Box 27)
- McDermott, Anne T. (Box 27)
- Morreale, Rose (Box 27)
- Morse, Martha W. (Wemple) (Box 27)
- Nytko, Darlene (Box 27)
- Pirenne, Thea (Box 27)
- Ruhe, Hope (Box 27)
- Shio, Helen (Box 27)
- Smarz, Jean (Box 27)
- Smith, Katharine (Box 27)
- Van Hook, Lucy (Box 27)
- Ward, Cynthia (Box 27)
- Weaver, James (Box 27)
- Winberry, Anne (Box 27)
- Wolf, Joel (Box 27)
- Woolley, Stephen (Box 27)
- Personnel, General, 1969, 1976 (Box 27)
- Curricula Vitae for Lab, 1976 (Box 27)
- Personnel, Prospectives, 1981 (Box 27)
- Kopito, Ron R. (Box 27)
- Personnel Prospectives, Extinct, 1978-1980 (Box 27)
- Bar-nun, Shoshana (Box 27)
- Brodie, David (Box 27)
- Cohen, Rochelle (Box 27)
- Lee, Kong Ning (Conan) (Box 27)
- Derby, Albert (Box 27)
- Edmonds-Alt, Xavier (Box 27)
- Feigenson, Martin (Box 27)
- Grab, Dennis J. (Box 27)
- Hayes, Mary K. (Box 27)
- Tsung, Pi-Kwang (Box 27)
- Farb, Roderick M. (Box 27)
- Goldstein, Joseph L. (Box 27)
- Ghosh, Swapan K. (Box 27)
- Kaplan, Arnold (Box 27)
- Koide, Sumi (Box 27)
- Lockshin, Richard A. (Box 27)
- Mercurio, Arthur (Box 27)
- Omholt, Paul E. (Box 27)
- Suzuki, Yasuo (Box 27)
- Tsao, Dean (Box 27)
- Students (Not in the Lab), 1977 (Box 27)
- Grecco, Frank (Box 27)
- Louvain Correspondence-Institute, General, 1963-1978 (Box 27)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
- Preparation of Glycogen from Mussels (Box 27)
- Peters-Dickie, John (Box 27)
- Berthet, Jacques, 1962-1973 (Box 27)
- Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 27)
- Hers, Gery, 1962-1972 (Box 27)
- Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 27)
- Jacques, Pierre, 1963 (Box 27)
- (Extinct Personnel), 1962-1978 (Box 28)
- Bartholeyns, Jacques (Box 28)
- Baudhuin, Pierre (Box 28)
- Beaufay, Henri (Box 28)
- Boon, Theirry (Box 28)
- Canonico, Peter G. (Box 28)
- Courtoy, Pierre (Box 28)
- Deprez (Box 28)
- Domagk, G. J. (Box 28)
- Eeckhout, Yves (Box 28)
- Gibbons, W. A. (Box 28)
- Grey, Howard M. (Box 28)
- Heremans, J. F. (Box 28)
- Masson, Pierre (Box 28)
- Nossal, Gus J. V. (Box 28)
- Remacle, Jose (Box 28)
- Louvain Personnel, 1964-1981 (Box 28)
- Sellinger, Otto Z. (Box 28)
- Stauber, William T. (Box 28)
- Symann, Michael L. (Box 28)
- Trouet, Andre (Box 28)
- Tulkens, Paul (Box 28)
- Vaes, Gilbert (Box 28)
- van der Rest, Michel (Box 28)
- Van Hoof, Francois (Box 28)
- Prospective Personnel, Louvain, 1969-1973 (Box 28)
- Bunce, George E. (Box 28)
- Cline, Martin J. (Box 28)
- Delvin, Edgard (Box 28)
- Morris, Margot (Box 28)
- Tolbert, N. E. (Box 28)
- Personnel and Applications, 1962-1973 (Box 28)
- Bird, John W. C. (Box 28)
- Burns, Gale (Box 28)
- Hardman, Joel G. (Box 28)
- Horowitz, Bruce (Box 28)
- Lequire, Virgil (Box 28)
- Miller, Fritz (Box 28)
- Schultz, ,R. L. (Box 28)
- Spier, R. E. (Box 28)
- Roelants (Box 28)
- Fripiat, J. J. (Box 28)
- Miscellaneous (Box 28)
- Louvain Conference, 1968 September 16-20 (Box 28)
- Louvain, Summer School of FEBS (Federation of European Biochemical Societies), 1965 June 8-18 (Box 28)
- Cell Biology Course, Cell Fractionation, 1973 (Box 28)
- Course on Cell Fractionation (Box 28)
- Cell Biology Course on Lysosomes (Box 28)
- Bioenergetics, 1971-1974 (Box 28)
- Organic Chemistry and Biochemistry, 1972-1975 (Box 28)
- Former Members of (the) Lab of Miklós Müller, 1979-1992 (Box 28)
- Baggiolini, Marco (Box 28)
- Beyer, Carl (Box 28)
- Bowers, William E. (Box 28)
- Cary, Joan M. (Box 28)
- Chudzik, Jerzy (Box 28)
- Corbacioglu, Nuriza (Box 28)
- Crisp, Robin (Box 28)
- Despommier, Dickson (Box 28)
- Di Domenico, Lucinda (Box 28)
- Else, Anthony J. (Box 28)
- Etzion, Zipora (Box 28)
- Associates, Former, A-G, 1979-1994 (Box 28)
- Brul, Stanley (Box 28)
- Cohen-Webb, Hope (Box 28)
- Declerck, Paul (Box 28)
- Fowler, Stanley (Box 28)
- Francioli, Patrick (Box 28)
- Gorrell, Tom (Box 28)
- Gyang, Fred (Box 28)
- Associates, Former, H-L, 1974-1997 (Box 28)
- Hou, Guang-Pei (Box 28)
- Hrdỳ, Ivan (Box 28)
- Jacobs, Gerarda (Paul Declerck's Wife) (Box 28)
- Jaikaria, Navdeep (Box 28)
- Jenkins, Tim (Box 28)
- Johnson, Patricia, 1986-1994 (Box 28)
- Laenge, Siegfried, 1988-1994 (Box 28)
- LaRusso, Nichols (Box 28)
- Lazarow, Paul (Box 28)
- Liebelson, Jerry (Box 28)
- Lindmark, Don, 1974-1989 (Box 28)
- Associates, Former, L-M, 1971-1991 (Box 29)
- Lederer, David A. (Box 29)
- Leroy, Marianne (Box 29)
- Lindmark, Donald G. (Box 29)
- Lo, Cecilia (Box 29)
- Mack, Steven (Box 29)
- Marczak, Regis (Box 29)
- Mortensen, Richard (Box 29)
- Murray, Marianne (Box 29)
- Obsolete Applications to Our Department, 1993-1997 (Box 29)
- Couzinet, Sabine (Box 29)
- Matussek, Karl (Box 29)
- Former Associates, 1975-1993 (Box 29)
- Lloyd, David (Box 29)
- Mack, Stephen R. (Box 29)
- Magenheim, Bryan (Box 29)
- Marczak, Regis (Box 29)
- McLaughlin, John, 1975-1989 (Box 29)
- Former Associates, 1982-1996 (Box 29)
- Mertens, Emmanuel, 1988-1994 (Box 29)
- Markus, Anton (Box 29)
- Mulready, Deborah E. (Box 29)
- Murray, Marianne (Box 29)
- Omer, El-Fadil E. (Box 29)
- Perkins, Margaret (Box 29)
- Former Associates, 1983-1994 (Box 29)
- Pirson, Philippe and Dominique (Box 29)
- Sam-Yellowe, Tobili (Box 29)
- Santiago, Lucia Richter (Box 29)
- Searle, Stephen (Box 29)
- Former Associates, 1984-1996 (Box 29)
- Sher, Audrey (Box 29)
- Soave, Rosemary (Box 29)
- Steinbüchel, Alexander (Box 29)
- Sullivan, Cathleen Patricia (Box 29)
- Torres-Munoz, Jorge (Box 29)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Applications/Benno ter Kuile, 1998-1999 (Box 29)
- Former Associates, 1981-1994 (Box 29)
- Viscogliosi, Eric (Box 29)
- Weber, Christopher (Box 29)
- Wong, David (Bronx High School of Science Student) (Box 29)
- Weiss, Martin (Box 29)
- Yarlett, Nigel (Box 29)
- Cornell, 1982-1987 (Box 29)
- Adjunct Position at Cornell (Box 29)
- B. H. Kean Course in Tropical Medicine (Box 29)
- Center for Disease Control (CDC) Susceptibility Evaluation (for Contracts, see Grants-CDC), 1981-1986 (Box 29)
- Center for Disease Control (CDC), Trip to Columbus, Ohio (Box 29)
- CSC Correspondence (Box 29)
- Drugs, Various, 1981-1995 (Box 30)
- Searle (Box 30)
- Searle, Washington, D.C. Meeting, 1994 September 22-23 (Box 30)
- Searle, Subhash Desai (Food and Drug Administration (FDA) Hearing) (Box 30)
- Pfizer (Box 30)
- Albany College of Pharmacy, Handbook of Medicinal Chemistry (Box 30)
- Farmitalia Carlo Erba, 1984 (Box 30)
- Isotopes Given to Miklós (Lab Safety Forms) (Box 30)
- Solco Basle Ltd., T. Vaginalis Vaccine (Box 30)
- Equipment, 1974-1989 (Box 30)
- Requests to Purchase (Box 30)
- Requests to Transfer Equipment (Box 30)
- Quotations and Correspondence on Equipment (Box 30)
- Dionex Ion Chromatograph (Box 30)
- Electrophoresis Equipment (Box 30)
- Millipore Pellicon Cassette System (Box 30)
- Polarograph (Box 30)
- Mass Spectrometry (Box 30)
- Exchange Programs, 1985-1992 (Box 30)
- Post Chech Exchange (Box 30)
- Czech Exchange Program, 1986 (Box 30)
- Exchange Program at Rockefeller University (Box 30)
- Human Investigations, Approval, 1981-1984 (Box 30)
- Human Investigations, 1981 (Box 30)
- Human Investigations, 1982-1984 (Box 30)
- Illustrations, 1978-1985 (Box 30)
- Copyrights of Miklos' Illustrations (Box 30)
- Material for Slides, 1981 November (Box 30)
- Donne (Box 30)
- Reviews of Applications for Grants/Fellowships, National Institute of Health (NIH) Fellowship Study Group, 1984-1993 (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Study Group, General Business, 1984-1987 (Box 30)
- BI3, (Biomedical Sciences Study Section, Subcommittee 3), 1984 January 30 (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Study Gorup, 1984 September (Box 30)
- BI3, 1984 May 8-10 (Box 30)
- Reviews of Applications for Grants/Fellowships, National Institute of Health (NIH) Fellowship Study Group, 1984-1993 (Box 30)
- Müller, National Institute of Health (NIH) Study Group, 1985 May (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Study Group, 1985 Janaury (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Study Section, 1986 January 27 (Box 30)
- Evaluations of Applicants to Rockefeller University (RU) PhD Program, 1982-1992 (Box 30)
- Reviews of Grant and Fellowship Applications, 1982-1990 (Box 30)
- Medical Research Council of Canada (Box 30)
- Venereal Diseases Research Fund (Box 30)
- National Science Foundation (NSF) Questionnaire for Reviewers of Grant Applications (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) 1982, Reviews for Grants (Box 30)
- Special Study Section, Arlington, Virginia, Christensen, 1982 November 30 (Box 30)
- Thrasher Research Fund (Box 30)
- Hollander, D. H. (Box 30)
- Special Study Section, 1984 August 3 (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Ad Hoc Study Section, 1985 December 5 (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH), 1984 February (Box 30)
- Wellcome Trust, 1990 (Box 30)
- Review for Wellcome Trust, 1988 January (Box 30)
- Study Group, National Institute of Health (NIH), 1988 (Box 30)
- Materials Folder (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) R-1 and FSC, 1988 April (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Telephone Conference, Study Group, 1988 June 17 (Box 30)
- National Institute of Health (NIH), 1988 March 7 (Box 30)
- Students at Rockefeller, 1982-1990 (Box 30)
- Delaney, John (Box 30)
- Feder, Roslyn (Box 30)
- Herlands, Louis (Box 30)
- McGrath, Robert (Box 30)
- Olson, Julie, Thesis Committee (Box 30)
- Sudol, Anna (Box 30)
- Sudol, Marius (Box 30)
- Young, Ding-E (Box 30)
- Zychlinsky, Arturo (Box 30)
- MD/PhD Students, Lunch Presentations by Faculty Members (Box 30)
- Campanelli, David (Box 30)
- Teaching, 1989-1992 (Box 30)
- Parasitology Course, 1992 (Box 30)
- Cell Biology Course, 1992 (Box 30)
- Cell Biology Course, 1991 (Box 30)
- Cell Biology Course, 1989 (Box 30)
- Thesis Committee, 1991 (Box 30)
- Yue Ding (Box 30)
- WHO (World Health Organization) Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 30)
- WHO (World Health Organization) Correspondence (Box 30)
- Leishmania (Box 30)
- SWG (Scientific Working Group) (Box 30)
- WHO (World Health Organization), 1981 (Box 30)
- Photographs (de Duve and Lab), 1976-1984 (Box 30)
- de Duve Articles, 1984-1990 (Box 30)
- Recent Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 30)
- Miscellaneous, 2001-2003 (Box 30)
- New York, 2001-2003 (Box 30)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2003 (Box 30)
- Apartment, 2003 (Box 30)
- Fermi Lab, "The Singularities in the Origin and Evolution of Life", 2003 (Box 31)
- Commitment Refusals, 1978-1998 (Box 31)
- American Nobel Anniversary, Dinner Washington, D. C., 1988 December 9 (Box 31)
- American Society for Cell Biology, Atlanta, Georgia, 1985 November, 18-22 (Box 31)
- New York Heart Association Interview (Phone), Patrusky, 1980 September (Box 31)
- International Health Symposium, Kyung Hee University (Seoul, Korea), 1979 October 29-31 (Box 31)
- International Union of Physiological Sciences, Hungary, 1980 July 13-19 (Box 31)
- Program for Neglected Diseases of Mankind, Rockefeller University (RU), 1978 November 13-17 (Box 31)
- Council for International Organizations of Medical Sciences, Lisbon, 1978 November 29-December 1 (Box 31)
- Extinct Writing Commitments, 1967, 1970, 1973 (Box 31)
- Molecular and Cellular Biochemistry (Box 31)
- Extinct Writing Commitments, 1967, 1970, 1973 (Box 31)
- New England Journal of Medicine (Box 31)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell (Box 31)
- Manuscript, "Singularities:: Landmarks in the History of Life" by Christian de Duve (Box 31)
- Raleigh-Durham, 2003 (Box 31)
- Photographs and Glass Slides (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published) (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 31)
- La Recherche Atomes (Box 31)
- de Duve, Christian, et al, Lysosomotropic Agents (Box 31)
- Shio et al, Lysosomes of the Arterial Wall IV (Box 31)
- Lindmark and Müller, Superoxide Dismutase in the Anaerobic… (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published) (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 31)
- Lindmark and Müller, Biochemical Cytology of Trichomonad…II (Box 31)
- Schneider, The Inner Mitochondrial Membrane – Composition… (Box 31)
- de Duve, Christian, Lazaro and Poole, Biogenesis and Turnover of Rat… (Box 31)
- Peters and Christian de Duve, Lysosomes of the Arterial Wall. II Subcellular Fractionation of Arotic… (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published), 1973 (Box 31)
- Lindmark and Müller, Hydrogenosome, A Cytoplasmic Organelle… (Box 31)
- Müller, Peroxisomes and Hydrogenosomes in Protazoa (Box 31)
- de Duve, Christian, Biochemical Studies on the Occurrence, Biogenesis… (Box 31)
- Lazaro and Christian de Duve, The Synthesis and Turnover of Rat Liver Peroxisomes V (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published), 1973 (Box 31)
- de Duve, Christian, Origin of Mitochondria (Box 31)
- Poole and Wibo, Protein Digestion in Cultured Cells. The Effect of… (Box 31)
- Bowers, Lysosomes in Rat Thoracic Duct Lymphocytes Fractionated by… (Box 31)
- Müller, Biochemical Cytology of Trichomonad Flagellates. I… (Box 31)
- Peters et al, Subcellular Fractionation Studies on Cells Isolated… (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published), 1972 (Box 31)
- Farquhar, et al, Cytochemical Localization of Acid Phosphatase Activity in Granule Fractions… (Box 31)
- Müller, Secretion of Acid Hydrolases and Its Intracellular Source (Box 31)
- Les Contraintes du Hasard, Christian de Duve (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published), 1971 (Box 31)
- McGraw Hill, Encyclopedia of Science (Box 31)
- de Duve, Christian, Perspectives Nouvelles de la Therapeutique (Box 31)
- de Duve, Christian, The Biogenesis of Lysosomes and Peroxisomes (Box 31)
- Lazaro and Christian de Duve, BBRC-Intermediates in the Biosynthesis of Peroxisomal Catalase in Rat Liver (Box 31)
- Tissue Fractionation Past and Present, Christian de Duve (JCB), 1971 (Box 31)
- Lysosomes in Tetrahymena Pyriformis. II. Intracellular Distribution…(Müller) (Box 31)
- Poole, B. The Kinetics of Disappearance of Labelled Leucene from the Free Leucene Pool… (JBC) (Box 31)
- Peters, T. J., Subcellular Fractionation of the Enterocyte with Special Reference to Peptide Hydrolases (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published), 1970 (Box 31)
- Baggiolini, Masson, Heremans and Christian de Duve, Association of Lacto-Ferrin with Specific… (Box 31)
- Paper on Academician Sissakian – for USSR Academy of Sciences, Christian de Duve (Box 31)
- Baggiolini, Hirsch, and Christian de Duve: Further Biochemical and Morphological Studies (Box 31)
- de Duve, Christian, The Role of Lysosomes in Cellular Pathology: Triangle (Box 31)
- Poole, Higashi, and Christian de Duve: Synthesis and Turnover…III. The Size Distribution… (Box 31)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts (Already Published), 1969-1970 (Box 32)
- Baggiolini, Separation of Granules (Box 32)
- Baudhuin, Hertoghe-Lefèvre, Christian de Duve, Differential Release of Alkaline Dioxyribonuclease… (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Introductory Remarks and Evolution of the Peroxisome (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Book on Lysosomes in Biology and Pathology: Dame Honor B. Fell and J.T. Dingle (Box 32)
- Fowler, S., Christian de Duve Digestive Activity of Lysosomes. III. The Digestion of Lipids (Box 32)
- Fowler, S., Lysosomal Localization of Sphingomyelinase in Rat Liver (Box 32)
- Muller, Lysosomal Hydrolases in Acanthamoeba (Box 32)
- Muller, Peroxisomes of Protazoa (Box 32)
- Muller, Acanthamoeba and Urate Oxidase (Box 32)
- The Synthesis and Turnover of Rat Liver Peroxisomes – I and II (Box 32)
- Trouet, A., Thesis (Box 32)
- Microsomes (BBRC) (Box 32)
- Microsome Paper (Box 32)
- Lysosomes and Storage Disease, Preface (Box 32)
- Commitment Refusals, 1976 (Box 32)
- Howard University Medical College, Washington, D. C. (Box 32)
- XII International Cancer Congress, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1978 October 5-11 (Box 32)
- Radio Diffusion, Télévision Belge; Institut des Emissions Françaises: Groupement Professionnel des Journalistes Scientifiques de Belgiques, ICP, 1976 October (Box 32)
- Second International Symposium on Alcohol and Aldehyde Metabolizing Systems, Philadelphia, 1976 October (Box 32)
- USSR, 1976 October (Box 32)
- Scientific Symposium to Honor Carl Cori, Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri, 1976 October (Box 32)
- Tenth International Congress of Biochemistry, Hamburg, Federal Republic of Germany, 1976 July (Box 32)
- Gordon Conference on Lysosomes, 1976 July (Box 32)
- American Society of Biological Chemists – 67th Annual Meeting, San Francisco, California, 1976 June (Box 32)
- Second EMBO Annual Symposium, Heidelberg, 1976 May (Box 32)
- Third International Symposium on Detection and Prevention of Cancer, New York, 1976 April 26-May 1 (Box 32)
- Apotekarsocieteten, Swedish Academy of Pharmaceutical Sciences: Bioactivation and Controlled Drug Release, Stockholm, Sweden, 1976 April (Box 32)
- Symposium on Cell Differentiation in Microorganisms, Leopoldina Halle, Germany, 1976 April (Box 32)
- Conference on Endocytosis and Intracellular Digestion, British Society for Cell Biology, University of Nottingham, England, 1976 April (Box 32)
- Cercle Européene de L'Université de Louvain, Louvain, Belgium, 1976 February (Box 32)
- Mack, Effect of O2 and CO2 on T. vaginalis and T. foetus, 1978 (Box 32)
- Poole, Ohkuma and Warburton: Accumulation of Weakly Basic Substances in Lysosomes, 1977 (Box 32)
- Poole, Ohkuma and Warburton, Some Aspects of the Intracellular Breakdown of Exog. and Endog. Proteins, 1977 (Box 32)
- Beyer and Bowers, Lymphocyte Transformation Induced by Chemical Modification of Membrane Components, I, 1977 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Cells Age – Are Lysosomes Among the Villains?, 1977 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, A Reexamination of the Physiological Role of Peroxisomes, 1977 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Ohkuma, Poole and Tulkens, The Intralysosomal Ph, 1979 (Box 32)
- McLaughlin, Lindmark and Müller, Inorganic Pyrophosphatase and Nucleoside Diphosphatase in the Parasitic Protozoon, Entamoeba Histolytica, 1978 (Box 32)
- LaRusso, Tomasz, Kaplan and Müller, Absence of Strand Breaks in DNA Treated with Metronidazole, 1977 (Box 32)
- Meingassner, Mieth, Czok, Lindmark and Müller, Assay Conditions…Resistance in T. foetus, 1977 (Box 32)
- McLaughlin, Lindmark and Müller, Mode of Action of Metronidazole on Anaerobic Microorganisms, 1977 (Box 32)
- Müller, Nseka, Lindmark and Mack, Effects of Two, Four-Dinitrophenol, 1978 (Box 32)
- The Fate of Plasma Membrane During Endocytosis. I and II, Schneider, Tulkens, Christian de Duve and Trouet, 1979 (Box 32)
- Lloyd, Lindmark and Müller, The Adenosine Triphosphatase of T. foetus, 1979 (Box 32)
- Fowler, Shio, Haley, Characterization of Lipid-Laden Aortic Cells…IV, Invest. of Microphange-Like Properties…, 1979 (Box 32)
- LaRusso and Fowler, Acid Hydrolases in Rat Bile – Hepatocyte Exocytosis… (Box 32)
- Shio, Haley and Fowler, Characterization of Lipid-Laden Aortic Cells from Cholesterol-Fed Rabbits, 1979 (Box 32)
- Fowler and Christian de Duve, Nature, Location, and Mode of Formation of Intracellular Deposits in Atherosclerotic Lesions, 1979 (Box 32)
- Lloyd, Lindmark and Müller, Respiratory Components of T. foetus, 1979 (Box 32)
- Nseka and Müller, L'Action des Inhibiteurs de la Glycolyse Sur'Absorption (Box 32)
- McLaughlin and Müller, Purification and Characterization of a Low-Molecular Weight Thiol from…T. foetus, 1978 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Acta Clin. Belge. – Biologie Cellulaire de L'Arteriosclerose, 1978 (Box 32)
- LaRusso, Lindmark and Müller, Biliary and Renal Excretion, Hepatic Metabolism…, 1977 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, An Integrated View of Lysosomes Function, 1977 (Box 32)
- Berberian and Fowler, Subcellular Biochemistry of Human Arterial Lesions. I (Box 32)
- McLaughlin, Lindmark and Müller, Membrane-Bound Pyrophos. in Ent. hist., 1977-1978 (Box 32)